<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>font awesome icons on Eva Louise Dressel</title>
    <link>https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/designs/font-awesome-icons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in font awesome icons on Eva Louise Dressel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Eva Louise Dressel / dress.code</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 15:30:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/designs/font-awesome-icons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Blog React</title>
      <link>https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/portfolio/travel-blog-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 15:30:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/portfolio/travel-blog-react/</guid>
      <description>The final project of the Full Stack Web Development Program at Hamburg Coding School was also a travel blog but in React. I scored 15/15 points.
I could have built up on the previous blog, but decided to work from scratch. Only images and places made it from the first travel blog to the second.
The homepage is devided into a map with markers on one side and a collection of all preview cards of places I have visted on the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architect Website</title>
      <link>https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/portfolio/architect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 07:00:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evahamburgcodingschool.github.io/portefeuille/portfolio/architect/</guid>
      <description>For a medium-sized interior architecture office specialized in corporate office spaces, I conceptionalized and realized their website relaunch.
The website is made and runs on a site builder, thus is fully responsive. While resorting to the conventient drag and drop building block functionality of the builder, I still used a great deal of JavaScript code injections and custom CSS styling.
Several features were incorporated at the customer&amp;rsquo;s request. The navigation shows font awesome sourced icons on hover and active.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>